Finally, to finish up, the hub is where everything lives. So all
the screens that I showed you, there's a full synopsis of what's
going on inside of your, your.
personal life. And as I scroll down, I can see my quarterly
targets. I can see my monthly missions. I can see my power
plays for the weekend.
It shows my day. If I want to just do a daily
frame and really commit to something, I can do it right here
directly.
And everything is housed right here for you to see, to make
it powerful, to hold yourself accountable. This is a game of accountability.
This is a game of, I want more for myself, so I'm
going to take it upon myself to do it.
And this app makes it fully capable and possible to see it
and be clear through understanding that you can hide from any of
this.